A Finding Aid to the Fidel Danieli papers, 1962-1987, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Printed Material, 1969-1985; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 2.1 Linear feet Boxes 7-9
  The bulk of this series consists of exhibition announcements for artists, exhibitions in Los Angeles and California galleries and art venues, museums, and university galleries. There are also a few miscellaneous files on events and performances, and some magazines and clippings.
  This series is arranged as 4 subseries.
  3.1: Artists, 1969-1982
  3.2: Los Angeles Galleries and Art Venues, 1971-1982
  3.3: California Museums and University Galleries, 1976-1982
  3.4: Other Printed Material, 1970-1985
  - Artists, 1969-1982; 3.1; Archival Resource Key
    The material is arranged alphabetically by artist.
    The bulk of the material in this subseries consists of exhibition announcements and a few clippings for various Southern California artists.
    - A - Peter Alexander, Martha Alf, John Altoon, 1975-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - A - Oliver Andrews, Charles Arnoldi, Michael Asher, 1970-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - A-B - Watler Askin, Don Bachardy, J. Baldessari, 1969-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - B - Joel Bass, Billy Al Bengston, Ed Bereal, 1970-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - B - Tony Berlant, Gary Beydler, Bob & Bob, 1975-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - B - William Brice, Jerrold Burchman, Chris Burden, 1976-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - C - Greg Card, Karen Carson, Vija Celmins, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - C - Carl Cheng (John Doe Co.), Judy Chicago (Gerowitz), Max Cole, 1975-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - C - Ron Cooper, Mary Corse, Robert Cumming, 1976-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - D - Lowell Darling, Michael Davis, Ron Davis, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - D - Tony DeLap, David Deutsch, Guy Dill, 1972-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - D-E - Lawrence Dreiband, Tom Eatherton, Doug Edge, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - E-F - David Elder, Edie Ellis (Danieli), Claire Falkenstein, 1974-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - F - Jud Fine, Llyn Foulkes, Sam Francis, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - F-G - Vida Freeman, Walter Gabrielson, Denise Gale, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - G - William Gatewood, Carson Gladson, Joe Goode, 1975-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - G-H - Scott Grieger, Nigel Hall, Lloyd Hamrol, 1975-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - H - Helen and Newton Harrison, June Harwood, Maxwell Hendler, 1969-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - H - George Herms, Diana Hobson, Patrick Hogan, 1975-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - H - Tom Holland, Tom Holste, Channa Horwitz, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - I-J - Shiro Ikegawa, Robert Irwin, Sandra Jackman, 1969-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - J-K - Ynez Johnston, Joanne Julian, Matsumi Kanemitsu, 1977-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - K - Don Karwelis, Craig Kauffman, Caroline Kent, 1972-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - K - Claude Kent, Charles Kessler, Carl Knitig, Leonard Koren, 1975-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - L - Suzaane Lacy, Don Lagerberg, 1972-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - L - John Lees, Barry Leva, Linda Levi, 1975-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - L-M - Peter Liashkov, Peter Lodato, Mac McCloud, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - M - John McLaughlin, Jerry McMillan, Michael C. McMillen, 1975-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - M - Arnold Mesches, Robin Mitchell, Ed Moses, 1970-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - M-N - Selma Moskowitz, Bruce Nauman, Margaret Nielson, 1970-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - N-P - Maria Nordman, Pat O'Neill, Helen Pashgian, 1975-1979; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - P-R - Peter Plagens, Ken Price, Man Ray, Lance Richbourg, 1969-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - R-S - Allen Ruppersberg, Edward Ruscha, Betye Saar, 1973-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - S - John Schroeder, Stephen Seemayor, Joyce Cutler Shaw, 1975-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - S - Judith Simonian, Barbara Smith, Jean St. Pierre, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - S-T - Joynn Suzar, Masami Teraoka, Michael Todd, 1975-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - T-V - Joyce Treiman, De Wain Valentine, Judith Von Euer, 1971-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - W - Gordon Wagner, Doug Wheeler, Guy Williams, 1970-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - W - Jay Willis, Michael Wingo, Tom Wudl, 1976-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Y - Rita Yokoi, Richard Yokomi, Nancy Youdelman, 1975-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Z - Connie Zehr, Elynn Zimmerman, 1976-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Group Shows, 1977-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Performances, 1972-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Los Angeles Galleries and Art Venues, 1971-1982; 3.2; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries consists of exhibition announcements from various Los Angeles galleries and art venues.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by gallery name.
    - A - ACE, Adrienne Simard, Anhalt/Barnes, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - A - Art Space, Artworks, Asher/Faure, 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - B - Bernard Jacobson, Broxton, Bryon Weber, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - C - Charles Cowles, China Club, Cirrus, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - C-E - Claire Copley, David Stuart, Ellie Blankfort, 1976-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - F - Ferus, Floating Wall, Foundation for Art Resources, 1976-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - G-H - Gallery West, Gemini G.E.L., Herbert Palmer, 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - H-J - Hunsaker/Schlesinger, Irving Blum, Jacqueline Anhalt, 1971-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - J - James Corcoran, Jan Baum, Jancar/Kuhlenshmidt, 1977-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Janus Gallery, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - K-L - Kirk de Gooyer, L.A.C.E., L. A. Louver, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - L - Landau/Alexander, Larry Gagosian, Leopold/Gold, 1979-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - L-M - Los Angeles Museum of Art, Malinda Wyatt, Margo Leavin, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - M - Meghan Williams, Mirage, Mizuno, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - M-N - Molly Barnes, Museum of Contemporary Art, Neil G. Ovsey, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - N-O - Newspace, Nicholas Wilder, Oranges/Sardines, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - R - Re:vision, Roger Wong, Ron Salgado, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - R - Rosamund Felsen, Roy Boyd, Ruth S. Schaffner, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - S - Sanguine Suite, Simard Weber, Some Serious Business, 1977-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - S - Space, Stella Polaris, Swope, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - T-V - Thomas Lewallen, Tortue, Ulrike Kantor, Vanguard, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - California Museums and University Galleries, 1976-1982; 3.3; Archival Resource Key
    The bulk of this subseries consists of exhibition announcements from museums as well as the galleries and exhibition spaces at universities and colleges in California, not restricted to Los Angeles.
    This subseries is arranged alphabetically by the name of the museum or educational institution.
    - A - ARCO, Art Center College of Design, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - B - Brand Library, Baxter Art Gallery, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - C - California State Universities of Dominguez Hills, Fullerton, L.A., Northridge, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - C-G - Cedars-Sinai Medical Center, Craft & Folk Art Museum, Downey Museum, Grossmont College, 1976-1981; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - L - Long Beach Museum of Art, Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1976-1978; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - M - Mount St. Mary's College, Mount San Antonio College Gallery, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Municipal Art Gallery, 1977-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - M-N - Museum of Contemporary Art in Los Angeles, Newport Harbor Art Museum, 1976-1980; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - O-P - Otis Art Institute, Palomar College, Pasadena City College, Pierce College, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - S-U - San Diego State University, University of California Irvine, University of California Los Angeles, 1976-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - U - University of California San Diego Mandeville Gallery, University of California Santa Barbara, 1978-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Other Printed Material, 1970-1985; 3.4; Archival Resource Key
    This subseries consists of assorted printed material such as exhibition announcements, magazines, press releases, and clippings.
    The first two folders of exhibition announcements and auctions retained their original headings which groups the material by event type, the remainder of the printed material is organized by document type.
    - Concerts and Events, 1973-1977; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Auctions and Benefits, 1970-1982; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Journal 40th Issue, 1984; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Images and Issues, 1982-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - News Clippings, 1979-1983; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous, 1985; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)